<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">¿Qué flor es? +</string>

    <string name="synchronizing">Sincronización …</string>

    <string name="offline_mode">Modo offline</string>
    <string name="offline_mode_summary">requiere espacio adicional de 300 MB</string>

    <string name="search">Buscar</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <string name="synchronization_on_background">Synchronization will start on the background after application will restart on wi-fi network.</string>
    <string name="authentication_failed">Authentication failed.</string>
    <string name="camera_failed">No picture was taken.</string>
    <string name="gallery_failed">No picture was added.</string>
    <string name="observation_saved">Observation was saved.</string>
    <string name="observation_not_saved">Observation was incomplete thus it wasn\'t saved. Location or photo is misssing.</string>
    <string name="observation_delete">Delete observation</string>
    <string name="observation_delete_question">Do you want to delete the observation?</string>
    <string name="plant_observations">Observations</string>
    <string name="no_observations">There is no observation yet.</string>
    <string name="no_observations_login">Observations are available only for logged users. Please log in.</string>

    <string name="photo_delete">Remove photo</string>
    <string name="photo_delete_question">Do you want to remove photo from the observation?</string>
    <string name="photo_duplicate">Duplicate photo. Skipped.</string>
    <string name="subscription">Subscription</string>
    <string name="subscription_info">Shared observations are visible only for subscribed users.</string>
    <string name="subscribe">Subscribe</string>
    <string name="subscription_intro1">Your observation\'s date, location and note are saved and persisted across devices without subscription, but photos are stored only locally on the device. You will lose connection to them (even photo itself when you shot it from the application) when you clear data, reinstall or switch device.</string>
    <string name="subscription_intro2">You are about to subscribe for saving and persisting your photos across all your devices. With subscription you agree to share your observations with other subscribed users. You\'ll also be able to see their observations. All shared observations are anonymous and its note stays private and won\'t be shared. To simplify process your photos will be shared under CC0 (Creative Commons Zero) licence, so you also agree with this.</string>
    <string name="subscription_intro3">Based on these observations distribution maps will be created along with other, not yet implemented, goodies which will be accessible only for subscribed users.</string>
    <string name="subscription_intro4">If you still hesitate to hit the button below, there is a 30 days trial period for both subscriptions.</string>
    <string name="showcase_observation_title">Observations</string>
    <string name="showcase_observation_message">Create and save your observation. Every observation must contain date, location and at least one photo. Personal note is not mandatory.</string>
    <string name="showcase_switch_title">Own / Shared</string>
    <string name="showcase_switch_message">Switch between your own and shared observations.</string>
    <string name="showcase_camera_title">Camera</string>
    <string name="showcase_camera_message">Use camera to take a picture of the flower. Every observation must contain at least one photo.</string>
    <string name="showcase_gallery_title">Gallery</string>
    <string name="showcase_gallery_message">Choose already taken photo from your device. You can add observation with photo you took couple years ago. Every observation must contain at least one photo.</string>
    <string name="showcase_location_title">Location</string>
    <string name="showcase_location_message">Set or adjust location manually.</string>
    <string name="showcase_save_title">Save</string>
    <string name="showcase_save_message">Save your observation. Every observation must contain date, location and at least one photo.</string>
    <string name="my_filter_title">Mi filtro</string>
    <string name="search_by_photo">Buscar por foto</string>
    <string name="no_photo_search_login">La búsqueda por foto está disponible solo para usuarios registrados. Por favor Iniciar sesión.</string>
    <string name="photo_search_failed">La búsqueda por foto falló. Verifique su conexión a Internet y vuelva a intentarlo.</string>
    <string name="photo_to_search_by">Foto para buscar por</string>
    <string name="photo_search_note">Esta es una característica experimental que funciona solo en línea. A veces encuentra exactamente lo que estás buscando, a veces ni siquiera cerca. Confío plenamente en Google aquí ya que están haciendo todo el trabajo duro. A medida que pasa el tiempo, debería ser mejor y mejor, pero no fue construido principalmente para el reconocimiento de las flores. Úselo con prudencia y no juzgue toda la aplicación en función de este experimento. Por motivos de calidad, todos los resultados de búsqueda (no fotos) se guardarán.</string>
</resources>
