<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">E questo che fiore è? +</string>

    <string name="synchronizing">Sincronizzazione …</string>

    <string name="offline_mode">Modalità offline</string>
    <string name="offline_mode_summary">richiede oltre 250+ MB di spazio aggiuntivo</string>

    <string name="search">Ricerca</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <string name="synchronization_on_background">Synchronization will start on the background after application will restart on wi-fi network.</string>
    <string name="authentication_failed">Autenticazione fallita.</string>
    <string name="camera_failed">No picture was taken.</string>
    <string name="gallery_failed">Nessuna foto aggiunta.</string>
    <string name="observation_saved">Osservazione salvata.</string>
    <string name="observation_not_saved">Observation was incomplete thus it wasn\'t saved. Location or photo is misssing.</string>
    <string name="observation_delete">Cancella osservazione</string>
    <string name="observation_delete_question">Vuoi cancellare l\'osservazione?</string>
    <string name="plant_observations">Osservazioni</string>
    <string name="no_observations">Non ci sono ancora osservazioni.</string>
    <string name="no_observations_login">Le osservazioni sono valide solo per gli utenti loggati. Per favore, effettua il login.</string>

    <string name="photo_delete">Rimuovi foto</string>
    <string name="photo_delete_question">Vuoi rimuovere la foto dall\'osservazione?</string>
    <string name="photo_duplicate">Duplicate photo. Skipped.</string>
    <string name="subscription">Iscrizione</string>
    <string name="subscription_info">Shared observations are visible only for subscribed users.</string>
    <string name="subscribe">Iscriviti</string>
    <string name="subscription_intro1">Your observation\'s date, location and note are saved and persisted across devices without subscription, but photos are stored only locally on the device. You will lose connection to them (even photo itself when you shot it from the application) when you clear data, reinstall or switch device.</string>
    <string name="subscription_intro2">You are about to subscribe for saving and persisting your photos across all your devices. With subscription you agree to share your observations with other subscribed users. You\'ll also be able to see their observations. All shared observations are anonymous and its note stays private and won\'t be shared. To simplify process your photos will be shared under CC0 (Creative Commons Zero) licence, so you also agree with this.</string>
    <string name="subscription_intro3">Based on these observations distribution maps will be created along with other, not yet implemented, goodies which will be accessible only for subscribed users.</string>
    <string name="subscription_intro4">If you still hesitate to hit the button below, there is a 30 days trial period for both subscriptions.</string>
    <string name="showcase_observation_title">Osservazioni</string>
    <string name="showcase_observation_message">Crea e salva la tua osservazione. Le osservazioni devono riportare la data, la posizione e almeno una foto. Le note personali non sono obbligatorie.</string>
    <string name="showcase_switch_title">Own / Shared</string>
    <string name="showcase_switch_message">Switch between your own and shared observations.</string>
    <string name="showcase_camera_title">Fotocamera</string>
    <string name="showcase_camera_message">Usa la fotocamera per scattare una foto al fiore. Le osservazioni devono contenere almeno una foto.</string>
    <string name="showcase_gallery_title">Galleria</string>
    <string name="showcase_gallery_message">Scegli una foto sul tuo dispositivo. Puoi anche aggiungere un\'osservazione accompagnata da una foto scattata un paio di anni fa. Le osservazioni devono contenere almeno una foto.</string>
    <string name="showcase_location_title">Location</string>
    <string name="showcase_location_message">Imposta o modifica manualmente la posizione.</string>
    <string name="showcase_save_title">Salva</string>
    <string name="showcase_save_message">Salva la tua osservazione. Le osservazioni devono contenere la data, la posizione e almeno una foto.</string>
</resources>
